Division of Invertebrate Zoology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Labels, 1864-Present; Series II
  - Original Object Labels. These are archived original labels removed from specimens., 1864-Present; 000984
    - Original Object Labels. Original label for YPM No. 5619, Gammarus pulex., 006539
    - Original Object Labels. Original label for YPM No. 8752, Eocyzicus deterrana., 006545
  - Slide Box Labels. Archived labels from the Microslide IMLS project., 1864-Present; 000983
    - Slide Box Label. Possible slide box label. Det A. H. Verrill. Dec. 1906 for drwaings. Setae and uncini, Pseudovermilia pileum Type, Paravermilia bermudensis Type, Subprotula longiseta Type, Salmacinopsis setosa Type, Eucarphus serratus Type, Eupomatus elegans Type, Hydroides bispinosa Type, Hydroides parvus, Pomatostegus brachysoma, 002804
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Univ. Miami Storr Coll., 1864-Present; 000011
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Porifera--Western North Atlantic Merrill Collection., 1864-Present; 000012
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: E. Leigh Coll., A Dragovich, USN Series, 1864-Present; 000013
    - Slide Box Labels. Internal label of slide box: Chukchi Sea Coll., 1864-Present; 000014
    - Slide Box Labels. Internal label of slide box, 1864-Present; 000015
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Jamaica-North Coast, 1864-Present; 000016
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: British Virgin Islands, 1864-Present; 000017
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Porifera - So. New England, 1864-Present; 000018
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box, Panacea, Florida Rudloe Coll., 1864-Present; 000019
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box, Jamaica-North Coast, 1864-Present; 000020
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: JAMAICA - NORTH COAST, 1864-Present; 000021
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels: Canal Zone, J. Jackson coll., 1864-Present; 000022
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Gulf of Calif and Cont. Slope, Scripps Inst. Oceongr. Coll., 1864-Present; 000023
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: New Zealand Porifera, 1864-Present; 000024
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Palau, 1864-Present; 000025
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Palau, 1864-Present; 000026
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Agelas spp. slides from D. J. Faulkner, 1864-Present; 000027
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box; F.L. Nicholson coll. - 1980 Off Georgia, 1864-Present; 000028
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal label of slide box; Jon Witman Collections - Gulf of Maine / St. Croix, 1864-Present; 000029
    - Slide Box Labels. Internal label of slide box; Fisheries Research Board, 1864-Present; 000030
    - Slide Box Labels. Internal label of slide box, 1864-Present; 000031
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Gulf of Alabama- Brenda Shaw, 1864-Present; 000032
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Porifera - Bimini IV, 1864-Present; 000033
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Porifera - Bimini I, 1864-Present; 000034
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: 172586 Marshall Is., 1864-Present; 000035
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Kapinga-Marangi, 1864-Present; 000036
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Porifera - Bimini II, 1864-Present; 000037
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Porifera - Bimini III, 1864-Present; 000038
    - Slide Box Labels. Internal label of slide box. PE & MP, 1864-Present; 000039
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: CPB1-36, 1864-Present; 000040
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Pacific Islands. Most likely from specimens in the USNM., 1864-Present; 000041
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Jamaica - North Coast, 1864-Present; 000042
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Axinellida - Jamaica, 1864-Present; 000043
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Jamaica - North Coast, 1864-Present; 000044
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box: Jamaica - Clionidae, 1864-Present; 000045
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box Jamaica Clionidae, 1864-Present; 000046
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. MPe-69 (2), MPb-69 (2), HB-69 (2), YPM No. 5510} [YPM No. 5164, 1864-Present; 000047
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box: Bimini, 1864-Present; 000048
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Plakortis Sp. 1 - Reddish West Indies TYPES, 1864-Present; 000049
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. BIMINI, 1864-Present; 000050
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Haliclona viridis, etc., 1864-Present; 000051
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PUERTO RICO V 4453A - 4487, 1864-Present; 000052
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PUERTO RICO IV 4416A - 4452, 1864-Present; 000053
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PUERTO RICO III 4381A - 4415B, 1864-Present; 000054
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PUERTO RICO II 4353B - 4380B, 1864-Present; 000055
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PUERTO RICO I 4322 - 4353A, 1864-Present; 000056
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. GOLD COAST G-112-163, 1864-Present; 000057
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. GOLD COAST G-60-111, 1864-Present; 000058
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. GOLD COAST G-1-59, 1864-Present; 000059
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Discovery Bay 1968 - III, 1864-Present; 000060
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. DISCOVERY BAY, 1864-Present; 000061
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. DISCOVERY BAY 1968 - I, 1864-Present; 000062
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. ENEWETAK SPONGES - J. Lamberson. The numbers and identifications on the inernal labeling are NOT refering to the slides found in the box., 1864-Present; 000063
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Puget Sound T. L. simpson, Collector, 1864-Present; 000064
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Bimini Collection, 1864-Present; 000065
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Bimini Collection, 1864-Present; 000066
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box., 1864-Present; 000067
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Biemma, 1864-Present; 000068
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Biemma, 1864-Present; 000069
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PORIFERA-EUROPE, 1864-Present; 000070
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Slides of type specimens from other museums US and foreign, 1864-Present; 000071
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Guam, 1864-Present; 000072
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. BRAZ 1-48, 1864-Present; 000073
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. MEXICO Bonet Collection, 1864-Present; 000074
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Trinidad - R. Hubbard "I" Series - "IR" series, 1864-Present; 000075
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera of Mexico, 1864-Present; 000076
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera of Mexico, 1864-Present; 000077
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Brazil No. 96-100 Puerto Rico SF 1-31, 1864-Present; 000078
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera - Monteray Peninsula YPM Nos. 1247 - 54; 1450 - 60, 1864-Present; 000079
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Puerto Rico Collections made by Sam Fuller in 1974. PR-1 + PR-3 Series, 1864-Present; 000080
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Ypm Nos. 7765, 4692, 5145, 5146, MCZ 6072, 1864-Present; 000081
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. YPM Nos. 7948B, 7982, 7983 DB - I8 (68), DB - 26 (68), SYC, LEUC, 1864-Present; 000082
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Puerto Rico 1968-II, 1864-Present; 000083
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Puerto Rico 1968-II, 1864-Present; 000084
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Curacao YPM Nos. 8263 - 8312, 1864-Present; 000085
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Jamaica - deep water, 1864-Present; 000086
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Ectyoplasia ferox (D. M.), 1864-Present; 000087
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. BRAZ 49-95, 1864-Present; 000088
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Florida Porifera Jack Rudloe Collections, 1864-Present; 000089
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Nekton Beta Cruises, Jamaica, 1864-Present; 000090
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Misc, 1864-Present; 000091
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Misc, 1864-Present; 000092
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Misc, 1864-Present; 000093
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Misc, 1864-Present; 000094
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Fisheries Research Board, 1864-Present; 000095
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Axinellida - Trinidad, 1864-Present; 000096
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Curacao IV Hummelinck, Coll, 1864-Present; 000097
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera - Brazil (J. Laborel), 1864-Present; 000098
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Curacao V Hummelinck, Coll, 1864-Present; 000099
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Curacao III Hummelinck, Coll, 1864-Present; 000100
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Curacao I Hummelinck, Coll, 1864-Present; 000101
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Curacao II Hummelinck, Coll, 1864-Present; 000102
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Misc, 1864-Present; 000103
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. RIS 1-24 Californian Collection, 1864-Present; 000104
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Gulf of Campeche Collection 1955 Paper, 1864-Present; 000105
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Petrosia; Xestospongia, 1864-Present; 000106
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Curacao - J.H. Stock Coll. Alacran Reef Coll., 1864-Present; 000107
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera - Brazil, 1864-Present; 000108
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Virgin Is. 5841-5849, 1864-Present; 000109
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Albatross III; Cruise 31A Off North Carolina, 1864-Present; 000110
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. CARMEL CANYON, CALIF. COLOMBIA ALBATROSS III, Cruise 31A (N.C.) 1098->1109, 1864-Present; 000111
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera - virgin Is. From fish stomachs + artificial reef, 1864-Present; 000112
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Virgin Islands Collection - J. Randall, 1864-Present; 000113
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Plakortis - West Indies Histological Sections, 1864-Present; 000114
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Jamaica Puerto Rico PRB Series - III, 1864-Present; 000115
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Jamaica Puerto Rico PRB Series II, 1864-Present; 000116
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Trinidad Sponges - R. Hubbard "A" Series, 1864-Present; 000117
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. D and M Colls, 1864-Present; 000118
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Naples Series - Plymouth Series de Laubenfels Collection, 1864-Present; 000119
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Dysidea crawshayi Micrioc. schoenus, 1864-Present; 000120
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. ALBATROSS III; Cruise 31A Off North Carolina 1108-1149, 1864-Present; 000121
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Jamaica Puerto Rico PRB Series, 1864-Present; 000122
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Ifaluk Sponges II, 1864-Present; 000123
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Europe Comparative Mat. Greece G. Watson Coll., 1864-Present; 000124
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Ifaluk Sponges I, 1864-Present; 000125
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PORIFERA - BRAZIL, 1864-Present; 000126
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Sponges from fish stomachs West Indies - III, 1864-Present; 000127
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Sponges from fish stomachs Virgin Is.; Puerto Rico - II, 1864-Present; 000128
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Sponges from fish stomachs - Virgin Is, 1864-Present; 000129
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Puerto Rico VI 4488A, 1864-Present; 000130
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Fibulia - like Sponges, 1864-Present; 000131
    - Slide Box Labels. External andinternal labels of slide box. Plakortis - West Indies, 1864-Present; 000132
    - Slide Box Labels. internal labels of slide box. Chondrilla Chondrosia, 1864-Present; 000133
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Stelletta (Forbes Coll.), 1864-Present; 000134
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Caribbean Porifera Misc Coll., 1864-Present; 000135
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Ifaluk Sponges III, 1864-Present; 000136
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. GHANA R. Bassindale Collection, 1864-Present; 000137
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Lissodendoryx isodictyalis, etc. Mycale fibrexilis, 1864-Present; 000138
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Keratosa, 1864-Present; 000139
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera Great Barrier Reef, Australia Lederic Coll., 1864-Present; 000140
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Unstained Sections Suberites, Prosuberites, Mycale, Cliona, 1864-Present; 000141
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera Puerto Rico SF-PR series, 1864-Present; 000142
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Puerto Rico Porifera YPM 4583 4602, 1864-Present; 000143
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Didiscus West Indies, 1864-Present; 000144
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera - Great Barrier Reef, Australia, 1864-Present; 000145
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PUERTO RICO PORIFERA ypm 4528 ypm 4582, 1864-Present; 000146
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Jamaica Puerto Rico, PRB Series - IV, 1864-Present; 000147
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera - Yale Peabody Museum Dry Collections, 1864-Present; 000148
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Hawaii Ref. G.M. Moore Albatross Colls., 1864-Present; 000149
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Hawaii Albatross Collections, 1864-Present; 000150
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Costa Rica 2-27; 590-597, 1864-Present; 000151
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Cacique Pt., Costa Rica, Poquito, Baja California, 1864-Present; 000152
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera - West Indies Humes Collection, Gulf of Calif + Cont. Slope, 1864-Present; 000153
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. HAWAII Albatross Collections, 1864-Present; 000154
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera - Great Barrier Reef, Australia, 1864-Present; 000155
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Sclerosponges YPM Nos. 6861, 6856, 6849, 6852, 1864-Present; 000156
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera - Palau Is. USNM Material Pacific Is. H. Caspers Coll., 1864-Present; 000157
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera - Palau Is. USNM Material, 1864-Present; 000158
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Suberites undulatus, Pachastrella, Hymeniacidon, Pachychalina, Mycale.Cliona viridis Haliclona - UK Australia, 1864-Present; 000159
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Ifaluk Non-Keratosa, 1864-Present; 000160
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Ifaluk - "Keratosa" - II, 1864-Present; 000161
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Ifaluk - "Keratosa" - II, 1864-Present; 000162
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Agelas Indo-pacific, 1864-Present; 000163
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. B5 & B6 (fixed in situ), YPM 8085, STOM. OR.A., STOM. APP., 1864-Present; 000164
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Porifera Great Barrier Reef, Australia Lederie Collection YPM No: 9201-9241, 1864-Present; 000165
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Mozambique Porifera A. P. Bowmaker; Porifera Collections of A.J. Bruce, 1864-Present; 000166
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Philippine Collections Doty, 1864-Present; 000167
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Thailand Sponges V Aimorn Chaicharn, 1864-Present; 000168
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Singapore YPM 6392 ->6409 YPM 2509 -> 2610, 1864-Present; 000169
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Singapore YPM 2547A -> 2599, 1864-Present; 000170
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Jamaican Sclerosponge Slides Philippe Willenz, 1864-Present; 000171
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Jamaican Sclerosponge Slides Philippe Willenz, 1864-Present; 000172
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PORIFERA - Miscellaneous Florida, British Columbia, 1864-Present; 000173
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Nigeria, 1864-Present; 000174
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Gold Coast G-164-180, 1864-Present; 000175
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PR-8, PR-9, DB-5I (68), YPM NO. 6225, YPM NO. 6509, 1864-Present; 000176
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. DICTYOCERATIDA, 1864-Present; 000177
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. BIII (z) LS, BIII (z) XS, BIII x-sect. BIV L-sect., BV L-S BI-FL, 1864-Present; 000178
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. BI (B) LS, BI (B) XS, BI (Z) LS, BIII (Z) XS, BIII (B) LS, BIII (B) XS., 1864-Present; 000179
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. al slides, 1864-Present; 000180
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Long Is. Sd. Calcarea, 1864-Present; 000181
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Calif Acad. Sci Collection, 1864-Present; 000183
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Calif Acad. Sci Collection, 1864-Present; 000184
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. Calif Acad. Sci Collection, 1864-Present; 000185
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Nemerteans Pacific Coast, 1864-Present; 000186
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Taeniosoma and Drepanophorus, Sandwich Islands, 1864-Present; 000187
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Suberites, 1864-Present; 000188
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Halichondria Dermal pores, sections, spicules, larvae, 1864-Present; 000189
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide boxes. A. E. VERRILL COLLECTION Yale Peabody Museum, 1864-Present; 000190
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide boxes. M. C. Z. Coll., etc., 1864-Present; 000191
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. PORIFERA - OREGON & WASHINGTON, 1864-Present; 000192
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. PORIFERA - KENT IS., NEW BRUNSWICK Summer, 1948, 1864-Present; 000193
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide boxes. MISCELLANEOUS PORIFERA off N.C., 1864-Present; 000194
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide boxes. BINGHAM OCEANOGRAPHIC COLLECTION Atlantic Coast, North America 2, 1864-Present; 000195
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide boxes. BINGHAM OCEANOGRAPHIC COLLECTION Atlantic Coast, North America, 1864-Present; 000196
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. 53ABCD FHM 51V X5X8X9, 1864-Present; 000197
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide boxes. 29194 B21-40 Protopelogonemertes hubrechti, 1864-Present; 000198
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. 311414, 311478A, 1864-Present; 000199
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide box. Exp. 2 mix OL 48L 8.0 ???, 1864-Present; 000200
    - Slide Box Labels. External label of slide box. Micrura, 1864-Present; 000201
    - Slide Box Labels. External labels of slide boxes. Nemerteans, 1864-Present; 000202
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. New South Wales YPM 1201 to 1224, 1864-Present; 000203
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide box. A.E. VERRILL COLLECTION Yale Peabody Museum, 1864-Present; 000204
    - Slide Box Labels. External and internal labels of slide boxes. A. E. VERRILL COLLECTION Yale Peabody Museum, 1864-Present; 000205